Class of 1939 Records, 1935-2004
Smith College Archives
Class of 1939 Records
1935-2004
Smith College. Class of 1939.
RG 80 UUID:6f1e6bb7-0d25-480a-b9d1-bc28410ee253
12 boxes (8.3 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1939.
Historical Note
The Class of 1939 was the sixty-first graduating class of Smith College.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Class of 1939 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1939, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1939 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Commencement 1939 (Box 2112, Folder 1)
- Commencement Dramatics 1939 (Box 2112, Folder 2)
- Commencement Music 1939 (Box 2112, Folder 3)
- Commencement Photographs 1939 (Box 2112, Folder 4)
- Freshman Handbook 1935-1936 (Box 2112, Folder 5)
- Groups 1935-1939 (Box 2112, Folder 6)
- Hoop Rolling 1939 (Box 2112, Folder 7)
- Ivy Day 1939 (Box 2113, Folder 1)
- Ivy Day-Music 1939 (Box 2113, Folder 2)
- Ivy Day-Photographs 1939 (Box 2113, Folder 3)
- Junior Prom 1938 (Box 2113, Folder 4)
- Junior Ushers 1938 (Box 2113, Folder 5)
- Last Chapel 1939 (Box 2113, Folder 6)
- Class Letters 1956-2001 (Box 2113, Folder 7)
- Officers 1935-1939, 1957 (Box 2113, Folder 8)
- Rally Day 1939 (Box 2113, Folder 9)
- Reunions 1940 (Box 2113, Folder 10)
- Reunions 1945 (Box 2113, Folder 11)
- Reunions 1949 (Box 2113, Folder 12)
- Reunions 1954 (Box 2113, Folder 13)
- Reunions 1959 (Box 2113, Folder 14)
- Reunions 1964 (Box 2113, Folder 15)
- Reunions 1969 (Box 2113, Folder 16)
- Reunions 1974 (Box 2113, Folder 17)
- Reunions 1979 (Box 2113, Folder 18)
- Reunions 1984 (Box 2113, Folder 19)
- Reunions 1989 (Box 2113.1, Folder 1)
- Reunions 1989 (Box 2113.1, Folder 2)
- Reunions 1994 (Box 2113.1, Folder 3)
- Reunions 1994 (Box 2113.1, Folder 4)
- Reunions 1999 (Box 2113.1, Folder 5)
- Reunions 2004 (Box 2113.1, Folder 6)
- Senior Dramatics 1939 (Box 2113.1, Folder 7)
- Senior Prom 1939 (Box 2113.1, Folder 8)
- Songs n.d. (Box 2113.1, Folder 9)
- Sophomore Carnival 1937 (Box 2113.1, Folder 10)
- Sophomore Push Committee 1937 (Box 2113.1, Folder 11)
- Step Sings 1939 (Box 2113.1, Folder 12)
- Class Supper 1939 (Box 2113.1, Folder 13)
- Year Book 1939 (Box 2113.1, Folder 14)